Usage: gitzap [options] [command]

AI-powered Git assistant ΓÇö analyze staged changes, generate Conventional
Commits, and explain history.

Options:
  -V, --version      output the version number
  -h, --help         display help for command

Commands:
  analyze            Analyze staged Git changes
  commit             Generate AI Conventional Commit candidates from staged
                     changes
  history [options]  Show recent Git commits
  explain [ref]      Explain a Git commit in simple technical language
  setup              Configure or update your AI provider API key and model
  help [command]     display help for command
